Everybody has different sensing ability.
الجميع لدية قدرة مختلفة على الاستشعار
What you're about to see in this movie
ما انت على وشك رؤيتة بهذا الفيلم
view it with your psychic ability.
تظهر قدرتك النفسية
What reason that bring us here together?
ما سبب أحضارنا هنا معاً؟
Why do we meet certain people?
لما نلتقى ببعض الناس؟
Relate with some people?
تتصل مع بعض الناس ؟
Why?
لماذا؟
I think it's because of our own karmas.
اعتقد انة القدر
Whether it is good.
سواء كان جيداً
Or bad karma.
أو قدر سىء
In the past life or this life.
فى الحياة السابقة أو الحالية
Whatever karma you do to others
مهما كان قدرك مع الاخرين
You have to pay your debts.
يجب ان تدفع ديونك
Karmas
القدر
connect us in a chain...
...تتصل ببعضها من خلال سلسلة
endlessly.
الى ما لا نهاية
Until all the karmic debts...
...حتى يتم جمع الديون
are repaid.
ويتم سدادها
We all live to pay our life debts.
نحن جميعاً نعيش لنسدد ديوننا
But I never let karma dictate my life.
لكنى لم أترك ابداً القدر يقود حياتى
Why is it so?
لماذا هذا؟
Because I see karmas of the others.
لأنى أرى قدر الاخرين
Why did you say that?
لماذا قلت هذا؟
Do you think I don't dare to hit you?
هل تعتقد أنى لن أجرؤ على ضربك؟
Say it. Why don't you say it now?
قولها.لما لا تقولها الأن؟
Huh? Say it.
هاة؟قولها
How's that? Such a brat again?
كيف هذا؟ايها الفتى الشقى
I saw you'll fall to your death from the balcony!
رأيتك تسقطى من الشرفة وتموتى
Hey, come here.
انت.تعالى هنا
Nobody knows what karma will bring
لا أحد يعلم ما الذى سيحضرة القدر
until the day it get back to you.
حتى يعود اليوم لك
And when the day comes,
وعندما يأتى هذا اليوم
everybody'll ponder the same question
سوف يفكر الجميع بنفس السؤال
What karma did I do?
ما هو القدر الذى لدى؟
Who taught you to say that?
من علمك ان تفعل هذا؟
Why did you say that to me?
لماذا تقول هذا لى؟
Tell me how I'll die.
أخبرنى كيف سأموت
Tell me. Tell me. I'll die right here, right?
أخبرنى.أخبرنى.انا سأموت هنا.صحيح؟
You want me to die right now?
انت تريدنى ان اموت الأن.صحيح؟
Tell me how I'll die.
أخبرنى كيف سأموت
For me, I don't know what karmic debt I have.
بالنسبة لى.لا اعرف ما هو قدرى
And why I see other people's karmic debts.
ولما أرى قدر الاخرين
Karma only belongs to the doer.
القدر فقط ينتمى الى الفاعل
To intervene the wheel of karma is useless.
التدخل فى القدر لا طائل منة
Second Sight
النـــظرة الـثــانــية ترجمة:doaa92 Re-Synced By: MEE2day
Attorney, before we pass a verdict,
ايها المحامى قبل الحكم
do you have anything to say?
هل لديك شيء لتقوله ؟
No, sir.
لا.سيدى
So the court clears the case
تحكم المحكمة بشأن القضية
in which Mr.Niwat Pongpaisan
التى أتهم بها السيد :نيوات بايجيسون
is accused for rape and murder of Ms.Supa Jumdee.
بتهمة الاغتصاب والقتل للسيدة سوبا
Here's your pay and triple bonus money.
هنا راتبك ومال المكافأة
So it's true what they say,
اذاً صحيح ما يقولونة
Laws can't keep up with you.
القانون لا يمكن ان يتماشى معك
Mr.Niwat,
سيد:نيوات
you may get away with your case,
يمكنك ان تهرب من لقضية
but you can't run away from your karma.
لكن لا يمكنك ان تهرب من قدرك
Hello.
مرحباً
Jum? I have something to tell you.
جوم؟لدى شىء أخبرك بة
Hey Jate,
مرحباً جيت
wanna have fun with us?
تريد ان تمرح معنا؟
Get back to our thing.
لنعود الى ما كنا نفعلة
Jate, I also have something to tell you.
جيت.انا ايضاً لدى شىء أخبرك بة
You do?
انتى لديكِ؟
Don't tell me that...
...لاتخبرينى هذا
I wanna get married.
أنا اريد ان أتزوج
Let's get married, Jate.
لنتزوج جيت
There's a song.
هناك اغنية
There's a piano melody I wanna play to you.
هناك لحن أريد ان اعزفة من أجلك
To make you feel...
...لأجعلك تشعر
Thank you.
شكراً
I do need to find my laptop.
كنت سابحث عن جهاز الكمبيوتر
Lovers...
...حبيبتى
we know each other's mind.
نحن نعرف عقول بعضنا البعض
And you know how much I worrried about you?
وتعلم.كم قلقت عليك؟
I was so worried about the news
كنت قلقة جداً بشأن الاخبار
about that car crash on the bridge.
بشأن حادث السيارة على الجسر
Actually, I was driving on the bridge.
فى الواقع كنت أقود السيارة على الجسر
I was close to death too.
كنت على وشك الموت ايضاً
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Look, you know that
انظرى.انتى تعرفى هذا
accident can't hurt me, don't you?
الحوادث لا يمكن ان تأذينى.صحيح؟
It's you who might get
انها انتى من يمكن
an accident from this wet floor.
ان تُصابى بحادث بسبب الأرض الرطبة
You could have fallen down.
يمكنك ان تسقطى
Sorry.
أسفة
I came up with lyrics when I was washing my hair.
خطرت لي كلمات عندما كنت أغسل شعرى
Really?
حقاً؟
So your song's finished. Let me hear it.
اذاُ اغنيتك انتهت .دعينى أسمعها
Not yet. Only a few lines here.
ليس بعد.القليل من الأسطر هنا
It's the biggest accident ever on the Rama 8 bridge.
انها اكبر حادث من أي وقت مضى على الجسر راما 8 .
Some witnesses said
بعض الشهود قالوا
they saw Ms.Kaewkwan's car crosscut a taxi.
انهم رأوا سيارة السيدة "كيا خوان"تقف أمام سيارة الأجرة
Causing the taxi to hit tge would-be groom and bride
مما تسبب في سيارات الأجرة تصدم العروس والعريس
along with the photographer who was
جنبا إلى جنب مع المصور الذي كان
taking their pre-wedding photos and killed them all.
يلتقط صورهم وتم قتلهم جميعاً
The taxi got off balance and hit the bridge rail.
سائق السيارة فقد التوازن وصدم الجسر الحديدى
Causing the car that belongs to Mr.Niwat Pongphaisal,
مما تسبب في السيارة التي ينتمي "إلى السيد "نيوات
a ladies-man business man
رجل الأعمال
to crash with the taxi
ليصطدم بسيارة الأجرة
and kill the driver and passengers right on spot.
و قتل سائق والركاب على الفور
Mr.Niwat's car fell down into Chao Phraya River.
سقطت سيارة السيد الى أسفل نهر شياو فيرايا
Mr.Jate,
سيد جيت
please come to the meeting room.
أرجوك تعالى الى غرفة الأجتماعات
OK.
حسناً
Here you are.
تفضل
The Ms.Kaewkwan's case file.
ملفات السيد كون كوان
It's a new big case our boss ordered you to do.
انها قضية كبيرة جديدة رئيسنا أمرك ان تتولى أمرها
Thank you.
شكراً
And..
..ايضاً
Something wrong?
ما الخطب؟
Marisa,
ماريسا
Please wear a turtle-neck blouse and a pair of trousers tomorrow.
أرجوكِ ارتدى بلوزة برقية وسروال غداً
So all 3 parties will have a peace of mind.
لذلك كل الأطراف الثلاثة سيكون لديها راحة بال
What 3 parties?
من الثلات أطراف؟
Do as I told you.
أفعلى كما أخبرتك
It's the accident happened yesterday.
انها الحادثة التى حدثت البارحة
Yes, it's the hot news of today.
نعم.انها الاخبار المنتشرة اليوم
This is such a hot case. Why isn't Jane on it?
انها قضية منتشرة لماذا جين بها؟
She's good.
أنها جيدة
She doesn't do lawsuit cases.
انها لا تقوم بالدعاوى
Our client...
...عميلنا
Kaewkwan Wisitwanich, aged 16.
كى كوان يتراوح عمرها 16عام
Stepdaughter of Kue Wisitwanich,
ابنة كوى ويستيوانش
the founder of Wisitwanich Petroleum.
مؤسس ويستيوانش للبترول
The whole family live abroad, don't they?
العائلة كلها تعيش بالخارج.أليس كذلك؟
This case will bring a lot of money to our office.
القضية ستجلب مال كثير لمكتبنا
Yes.
نعم
Our boss said it gotta be your case.
رئيسنا قال انها يجب ان تكون قضيتك
And you can't fail.
ولا يمكنك ان تفشل
What's the matter?
ما الأمر؟
Having a headache again?
لديك صُداع مجدداً؟
I'll get you some pills then.
سأحضر لك بعض الحبوب
I'll be right back.
سأعود فى الحال
Mr.Jate. Now that you're here.
سيد جيت.الأن وأنت هنا
So you're working for Kaewkwan now?
اذاً انت تعمل لصالح "كى كوان"الأن؟
Right.
صحيح
She's a murderer.
انها قاتلة
She must have paid you to make her get away with the crime.
لابد انها دفعت لك لكى تخرجها من الجريمة
Just a suspect, not a murderer.
فقط مشتبة بها وليست مجرمة
Besides, Kaewkwan is still a juvenile.
بجانب"كى كوان"لا تزال يافعة
We're all the losers in this tragedy.
نحن جميعا الخاسرون في هذه المأساة .
Hey! But we've lost our family.
مهلاً لكن نحن فقدنا عائلتنا
Kaewkwan's still alive.
كى كوان "لا تزال على قيد الحياة"
She should be dead too.
هى يجب ان تموت ايضاً
Bastard! A damn lawyer always gets benefits either way.
نذل ! محام لعين دائما يحصل على فوائد في اي من الاتجاهين .
Do you have something to add?
هل لديك شىء تُضيفة؟
For this kind of news,
لهذة الأنواع من الأخبار
you reporters dare say you didn't get any benefit?
تجرؤى على قول ان الصحفيين لا يحصلوا على أى نوع من الفائدة؟
What are you looking at?
ما الذى تنظر إلية؟
I'm your lawyer. Your father hired me.
انا محاميكِ.والدك أستعان بى
How are you? Did you get hurt?
كيف حالك؟هل تأذيتى؟
What took you so long?
ما الذى اخرك كثيراً؟
Bring me back home. I wanna go back to my condo.
أعيدنى الى منزلى أريد ان أذهب الى منزلى
But I think you'd better stay here.
لكن اعتقد من الأفضل ان تبقى هنا
You want me to be here?
أنت تريدنى أن أكون هنا؟
People here look at me as if I'm a murderer.
الناس هنا تنظر إلى كما لو كنت مُجرمة
Why do you want me to tolerate it?
لماذا تريدنى أن اتحمل هذا؟
You have to bear it for a while.
يحمل ان تتحملى هذا لفترة
I'll get some reporters to report your case.
سأحضر بعض الصحفيين للأبلاغ عن حالتك
What?
ماذا؟
You're fired.
أنت مطرود
You can't fire me.
لا يمكنك ان تطردينى
I'm the only one who can save you from prison.
انا الوحيد الذى يمكنة ان ينقذك من السجن
And help you get away with what's after you.
وأساعدك من الهروب ممن يسعى خلفك
What are you talking about?
ما الذى تتحدث عنة؟
When the car crashed, you weren't sleeping.
عندما أصطدمت السيارة انتى لم تكونى نائمة
You just couldn't move, right?
انتى فقط لم تستطيعى التحرك.صحيح؟
That's what they did to you.
هذا ما فعلوة بكِ
Though you've survived this time,
اعتقد انكِ نجوتى هذة المرة
But eventually they'll get you.
ولكن في نهاية المطاف أنهم سينالوا منكِ
Nurse,
ممرضة
please put more bandages on her.
أرجوكِ ضعى المزيد من الضمادات عليها
We need a lot of bandages.
نحتاج الكثير من الضمادات
In this country, a person who has money never does any wrong.
فى هذة البلدة الشخص الذى يملك نقود كثير لا يفعل ابداً شىء خطأ
Is...
...هل
it true about the ghosts?
الامر صحيح بشأن الشبح؟
Yeah.
نعم
How do you know?
كيف تعرف؟
I see things ordinary people can't see.
أنا ارى اشياء لا تستطيع الناس العادية رؤيتها
Or don't wanna see.
أو لا يريدوا رؤيتها
Is there any in this room?
هل هناك شىء فى هذة الغرفة؟
I see a mummy.
انا أرى مومياء
You're just scaring me.
انت فقط تُخيفنى
No, I'm not.
لا.انا لست كذلك
But what will scare you..
...لكن ما سيخيفك
Is this.
هو هذا
Are you tired?
هل انت متعب؟
Give me a hug.
أعطنى عناق
Oh, too tight.
أوة.ضيق جداً
Jate.
جيت
Do you really have to do this case?
هل يجب حقاً ان تقوم بهذة القضية؟
I didn't want you to help the wrong doer.
لا  أريد منك أن تساعد الفاعل خاطئ .
Believe me.
صدقينى
She isn't guilty.
انها ليست مذنبة
All of what happened indicated that she's guilty,
كل ما حدث إلى ألأن انها مذنبة ،
she's innocent.
انها بريئة .
You don't belive what I say.
انت لا تصدق ما أقولة
Do whatever you want then.
أفعل ما تريد اذاً
It's just a job. Give me a hug now.
انة فقط العمل.,اعطنى عناق الأن
Kaewkwan
كى كوان
Hello?
مرحباً؟
Jate! Help me, ghost!
جيت.ساعدنى.شبح
Jate, help me.
جيت,ساعدنى
Oh, you really came.
أوة لقد أتيت حقاً
Is it fun?
هل هو مُضحك؟
Serve you right. You scared me with that ghost story.
لقد أخفتنى بقصة هذا الشبح
You gotta stay with me for tonight.
يجب ان تبقى معى الليلة
I'll take you home first.
سأخذك للمنزل اولاً
That's alright. I can go home myself.
لا بأس يمكننى نا أذهب للمنزل لوحدى
Jum.
جوم
Do you need a sleeping pill?
ها تحتاجى حبوب لتنامى؟
No.
لا
Are the dead really following me?
هل الموتى حقاً يتبعونى؟
Are they all here?
هل جميعهم هنا؟
There're 3 of them here.
هناك ثلاثة منهم هنا
How can I see them too?
كيف استطيع رؤيتهم ايضاً؟
Why do you wanna see them? Aren't you scared?
لما تريدى رؤيتهم؟ألستى خائفة؟
No.
لا
Bend down and look between your knees.
أنحنى لآسفل وأنظرى بين ركبتيكِ
You might see it.
ربما تشاهديهم
You're teasing me.
انت تختبرنى
If you took me serious, I might actually see them.
اذا اخذتنى بجدية ربما سأراهم
You'd better not.
من الأفضل ان لا تفعلى
It isn't a gift. It's a curse.
انها ليست هدية.انها لعنة
Get well soon.
تحسنى قريباً
Jate...
..جيت
Jate, help me..
...جيت.ساعدنى
Jate, help.
جيت.ساعدنى
I'll kill you.
سأقتلك
Jate..
...جيت
Jate.
جيت
Jate, help me.
جيت.,ساعدنى
Jate..
.,.جيت
Help me.
ساعدنى
What monster are you?
أى وحش انتى؟
My son's dead. Don't you feel anything?
أبنى توفى.هل تشعرى بشىء؟
So you're bailed out. Is it because Mr.Jate's power again?
اذاً لقد تم انقاذهل.هل هذا بسبب سلطة السيد جيت مجدداً؟
So the murderer won't take any responsibility?
اذاً القاتل لن يتحمل اى مسئولية؟
It's up to the court's judgment.
الامر متروك للمحكمة
If he allows her to be bailed out,
اذا سمح ببراءتها
it means my client won't run away.
هذا يعنى ان عميلى لن يهرب
Besides, she's just a suspect.
بجانب انها مشتبه بها فقط
Not a murderer.
وليس مُجرمة
Bitch, you killed my son.
عاهرة.لقد قتلتى ابنى
How could you say that, asshole?
كيف يمكن ان تقول هذا.ايها الأحمق؟
Bad bitch! Evil girl!
عاهرة سيئة.فتاة شريرة
Murderer.
قاتلة
You greedy lawyer.
ايها المحامى الجشع
You mean the defendant doesn't have to be punished?
تقصد ان المدعىعلية لا يجب ان يُعاقب؟
I believe in the laws.
انا اؤمن بالقانون
Let the court make the judgment.
اتركوا المحكمة تتخذ القرار
How could you say that?
كيف تمكنك قول هذا؟
Bastard. You asshole lawyer.
وغد.أيها المحامى الأحمق
Doesn't a life mean anything to you?
ألا تعنى الحياة شىء لك؟
This is the latest update at the court today.
هذة أخر أحداث المحكمة اليوم
This is such a heart-rendering case
انها حالة تحطم الفؤاد
that people are paying attention to.
..الناس تُعير الأهتمام لـها
We'll keep you posted on the case.
سنظل نطلعكم على اخر المستجدات فى القضية
If I do this, those ghosts will stop following me?
اذا فعلت هذا.هذة الاشباح ستتوقف عن تتبُعى؟
Not really.
ليس حقاً
But at least you did something.
لكن على الاقل انتى فعلتى شىء ما
So you won't just sit and be scared.
لذا لن تجلسى فقط وتكونى خائفة
It's just like buying a coffin for myself.
انها مثل شراء تابوت لنفسى
No,
لا
This one is reserved for someone else.
لقد تم حجز هذا لخص أخر
Father, you have anything protect us from evil,
أبتى.لديك أى شىء يحمينا من الشر
or ghosta, don't you?
أو الشبح.هل لديك؟
You do know too well. Nothing can protect you but yourself.
انت تعلم جيداً انة لا يمكن لشىء حمايتك سوى نفسك
I know that.
اعلم هذا
Why would you say or do something to comfort people?
لماذا تقول أو تفعل شيئا لراحة الناس؟
Just like other monks would do?
فقط كما يفعل الرهبان الأخرين؟
Can it really prevent ghosts?
هل يمكنها حقاً ان تحجب الأشباح؟
Hold your mind as hard as the rosary.
اعقدى عقلك كهذا العقد
And no evil can harm you.
ولا يمكن لشر ان يصيبك
Jate, are you hungry?
جيت.هل انت جائع؟
I can fix you something to eat.
يمكننى أن اصنع شىء لتتناولة
Why do you always look at me like that?
لماذا دائماً تنظر لى هكذا؟
You gave me the same look when we first met.
لقد نظرت لى نفس النظرة عندما تقابلنا أول مرة
You look familiar as if we'd met before.
انتى تبدى مالوفة كما لو أننا تقابلنا من قبل
Gotcha!
مسكتك !
Your ex-girlfriend, right?
صديقتك السابقة.صحيح؟
Your trick is as old as you.
خدعتك قديمة كثلك
Listen... don't get me wrong.
أسمعى...لاتفهمينى خطأ
No need to deny.
لاحاجة للنكران
Don't you like having a younger girlfriend?
ألا تحب ان يكون لديك صديقة صغيرة؟
Aren't you too young?
ألستى صغيرة جداً؟
I'm 20 years older than you.
انا أكبر منكِ بـ 20عام
Besides, I already have a girlfriend.
بجانب انى بالفعل لدى صديقة
You saw her, didn't you?
انتى رأستها.أليس كذلك؟
Nothing I would care of.
لا شىء لآهتم بة
It's my recipe.
أنها وصفتى الخاصة
Your enegy will be powered up.
سيتم تجديد طاقتك
I guesss you aren't scared now. Right?
اعتقد انكِ لستى خائفة الأن.صحيح؟
Good. So I can go home now.
جيد.اذاً يمكننى ان أذهب الى المنزل
Why do you gotta mention it? I'm getting scared again.
لما ذكرت هلا.؟اعتقد انى خائفة مجدداً
It's strange.
انة غريب
You didn't act like this the first time I met you.
انتى لم تتصرفى مثل أول مرة رأيتك بها
Do you know you were such a rascal that day?
هل تعرفى كم كنتى وغدة فى هذا اليوم؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح
I don't know why I feel so warm...
...لا اعلم.لما اشعر بالدفء
when you're around.
عندما تكون بالجوار
I think I better go now.
اعتقد يجب ان أذهب الأن
Have some rest.
نالى قسطاً من الراحة
I'll see you tomorrow.
أراكِ غداً
There's a song that I wrote.
هناك اغنية كتبتها
Jum.
جوم
Jate.
جيت
Coffee.
قهوة
Here you are.
تفضل
Thank you.
شكراً
Jum, don't think too much.
جوم.لا تفكرى كثيراً
Just a bad dream. It can't harm you.
فقط حلم سىء.لا يمكنة ان يؤذيكِ
Won't you believe me at all?
ألن تُصدقنى؟
I told you it wasn't just a dream.
أخبرتك انة لم يكون مجرد حلم
Not that I don't believe you,
ليس أنى لا اصدقك
but I've checked and found nothing.
لكنى تفحصت ولم اجد شىء
Good. With me, you see nothing.
جيد.معى.انت لا ترى شىء
I guess, with that girl, you'd see everything
اعتقد مع هذة الفتاة انت ترى كل شىء
What are you saying?
ما الذى تقولينة؟
She's my client and she's just a kid.
انها عميلتى وهى طفلة
Kaew
كى كوان
Jum, wait.
جوم.انتظرى
There's nothing between us.
لا يوجد شىء بيننا
Jate. Jate.
جيت.جيت
Jate. What's the matter? Mister.
جيت.ما الآمر؟
Jate. Mister.
جيت
Do you still have a headache?
هل مازالت تُعانى من الصداع؟
Not anymore.
ليس بعد الأن
Your symptom is caused by excessive brain pressure.
سبب حالتك هى الضغط المُفرط
Normally, we'd find it in a case of severe brain tumor.
عادة ، كنا نجد أنه في حالة ورم في المخ الشديد.
Kind of stange...
...غريب نوعاً ما
We found nothing unusual.
نحن لم نجد شىء غير عادى
If it's just a normal stress,
إذا كان مجرد الضغط العادي ،
I think you might be the most stressed
اعتقد انك أكثر شخص
person that the world ever seen.
مرهق أشاهدة فى هذا العالم
Sorry to ask this.
أسف على سؤالك هذا
What are you so stressed about?
ما الذى تجهد نفسك بة هكذا؟
I had a fight with my girlfriend.
لقد تشاجرت مع صديقتى
That must be a big fight.
لابد انة شجار كبير
Don't get too stressed.
لا تجهد نفسك كثيراً
Or your brain blood vessels will explode.
أو الاوعية الدموية فى المخ ستنفجر
Jum,
جوم
I'm not unfaithful.
أنا لست خائن
Those photos were taken when I was sleeping.
هذة الصور تم أخذها وانا نائم
You must be so tired that you were in deep sleep.
لابد انك كنت متعب جداً لأنك كنت عميق فى النوم
I don't fancy her.
انا لم أخطبها
She's just a kid so I just wanna help her.
هى مجرد طفلة لذا أريد أن أساعدها
That's all.
هذا كل شىء
Not that she looks like someone in the past?
ليس لأنها تشبة شخص ما فى الماضى؟
If you still wanna be with me,
أذا اردت ان تستمر فى كونك معى
withdraw from the case.
أنسحب من القضية
Oh, Jate.
أوة جيت
It's good you're here. Can you talk to the boss?
جيد انكِ هنا.هل يمكنك ان تتحدثى مع الرئيبس؟
I'd like to withdraw from the case.
أريد أن أنسحب من القضية
Why?
لماذا؟
It's none of your concern.
انه ليس من شأنك
Do as I told you.
أفعلى كما قلت لكِ
The police just called.
لقد أتصلت الشرطة للتو
They urged you to the crime scene.
يريدوك فى مسرح الجريمة
Another body was found.
لقد تم إيجاد جثة أخرى
OK.
حسناً
By the way, Marisa.
بالمناسبة.ماريسا
There's also a dead body here.
هناك ايضاُ جثة ميتة هنا
Where is that folder?
أين هذا الملف؟
Yes, sometimes it's seperated.
نعم أحياناً هى منفصلة
Here you are, Mr.Tasteless Lawyer.
ها انت.ايها المحامى
I've released the news.
لقد نشرت الخبر .
The public is angry with the defendant.
الجمهور غاضب مع المدعى عليه.
I really wanna know
أريد أن أعرف حقا
If you'd be able to help a murderer get away this time.
اذا كنت ستقدر على مساعدة القاتل ليخرج منها هذة المرة
Seems you like to see me lose the case
يبدو أنك تحب أن تراني أخسر القضية
more than seeing my client in jail.
أكثر من رؤية عميلى فى السجن
I must insist that
يجب أن أصر على هذا
your karma should have gotten you a long time ago.
قدرك يجب ان يحدث لك منذ وقت طويل
We all have our own karmas.
جميعنا لدينا أقدار
For some people, it gets them once and for all.
بالنسبة لبعض الناس ، فإنه يحصل لهم مرة واحدة وإلى الأبد.
But for some others,
لكن بالنسبة للأخرين
it just gradually eats their soul
انها تأكل روحهم تدريجياً
until there's nothing left.
حتى لا يتبقى منهم شىء
Inspector, I'm saying this with good intention.
مفتش ، أنا أقول هذا مع حسن النية .
You should stop eating snakes.
يجب عليك التوقف عن تناول الثعابين .
Snakes are cursed animals.
الثعابين حيوانات لعينة
They can devour your soul...
يمكنها ان تلتهم روحك
draining every bit of it.
وأستنزافها
My subordinates told you something, huh?
الرؤساء قالوا لكَ شىء ما.أليس كذلك؟
Keep your circus tricks for the court.
أحتفظ بحيل السرك للمحكمة
Up to you then.
الأمر متروك لك اذاً
Excuse me, I need to see my client's car.
أعذرنى يجب ان أرى سيارة عميلتى
Hey.
انت
That's alright. I'd like to walk downstairs.
لا بأس.سأستخدم السلالم للأسفل
A common mug like you gotta use the stairs.
شخص مثلك يجب ان يستخدم السلالم
For me,
من اجلى
an elevator.
المصعد.....
What the hell?
ماذا بحق الجحيم ؟
Hey!
مهلاً
What the...?
ما هذا؟
Vehicles from crime scenes.
السيارات من مسرح الجريمة .
Hello.
مرحباً
Where's the car from the latest accident?
أين السيارة من أخر مسرح للجريمة؟
Thank you.
شكراً
Every time you see a vision,
كل مرة تشاهد رؤية
You're having a severe headache?
يكون لديك صداع شديد؟
Are you alright, Jate?
هل انت بخير.جيت؟
Can I hold your hand?
هل يمكن ان امسك يدكِ؟
Why?
لماذا؟
If I hold someone's hand,
اذا أمسكت يد شخص ما
I'll see the past and future of that person.
سأرى ماشى ومستقبل هذا الشخص
And if I held your hand long enough,
واذا مسكت يدك لوقت كافى
I'd know why the ghost is after you.
سأعلم لما يسعى الشبح خلفك
Jate.
جيت
Jate, what's the matter?
جيت.ما الآمر؟
It didn't want me to see.
أنهم لا يريدوا منى ان أرى
Again.
مجدداً
No, you might be dead.
لا,انت يمكنك ان تموت
Jum.
جوم
Jate, It's her again.
جيت.انها هى مُجدداً
Am I gonna die here?
هل سأموت هنا؟
Jum,
جوم
remember that I love you.
تذكرى أنى أحبك
What I'm going to do is to help you from death.
ما أنا بصدد القيام به هو لمساعدتك من الموت .
So you have to trust me.
ولذلك عليك أن تثق بي .
You have to trust me.
عليك أن تثق بي
Calm down, Jum. Calm down.
اهدأى .جوم.أهدأى
Calm down.
اهدأى
You've escaped the moment of life and death.
لقد هربتى من لحظة الحياة والموت
When I pull you up,
عندما سحبتك للخارج
you'll be reborn.
تم ولادتك من جديد
From now on, nobody will be able to hurt you.
من الآن فصاعدا، لا أحد سيكون قادرا على يؤذيك .
But I saw her.
لكنى رأيتها
She's gonna kill me.
هى ستقتلنى
She's in the water, Jate.
انها فى الماء.جيت
Saw who?
رأيتى من؟
Can you come to the crime scene tomorrow?
هل يمكنك ان تأتى الى موقع الجريمة غداً؟
You'll find the missing body.
ستجد جثة مفقودة
This house is built for the newlyweds.
تم بناء هذا البيت لل عروسين .
But they died in the accident before they moved in.
لكنهم لقوا حتفهم في حادث قبل أن انتقل فيه
Are you sure you can stay here?
هل انتى متاكدة انة يمكنك البقاء هنا؟
Prepare food to pay homage to the spirit.
أعدى الطعام لتكريم الروح
Don't forget to light incense sticks.
لا نسى ان تشعلى البخور
Hey!
مهلاً
If you wish to take someone to be your own, be careful.
اذا كنتى تتمنى أن تأخذى شخص ليكون ملكك, كونى حذرة
My friend got a hair extension done.
صديقى حصل على شعر مجعد
And there's a night...
...وهناك ليلة
This girl told her...
...هذة الفتاة اخبرتة
The first kiss will tell you...
...القبلة الأولى ستخبرك
Will you love me? Will you..
...هل تحبينى؟هل
Bride and groom. For presentation shooting,
العروس والعريس. بجلسة التصوير
I'll like you to show your love to the audience.
أحب أن أظهر حبك للجمهور
Embrace each other. Look into each other's eyes.
احتضان بعضهم البعض . النظر في عيون بعضهم البعض .
And kiss.
وقبلة
Show them your love.
أظهرى لهم حبك
Good. Slowly. Slowly.
جيد.ببطء.ببطء
Good. And action!
جيد.تصوير
Bride and groom...
العروس والعريس
I'll like you to show your love to the audience.
أحب أن أظهر حبك للجمهور
Embrace each other. Look into each other's eyes.
احتضان بعضهم البعض . النظر في عيون بعضهم البعض .
I'll like you to show your love to the audience.
أحب أن أظهر حبك للجمهور
Embrace each other. Look into each other's eyes.
احتضان بعضهم البعض . النظر في عيون بعضهم البعض .
I'll like you to show your love...
...أحب ان أظهر حبك
Bride and groom, give me a sweet moment.
العروس العريس.اعطونى ذكريات حلوة
Good. Get closer to each other.
جيد.اقتربوا من بعضكم البعض
ExceHenL
رائع
Groom, look at your bride.
العريس.انظر الى العروس
And Bride, look at your man.
والعروسة انظرى الى رجلك
Excellent. I'll do the filming now.
بالضبط سأصور الفيلم الأن
Excellent. Hug each other gently.
ممتاز.عانقوا بعض بلطف
Kiss each other softly.
قبلوا بعضكم البعض بلطف
That's right. Gently hold each other's hands.
جيد.امسكوا أيدى بعض بلطف
Mr.Groom, hug your bride.
ايها العريس.عانق العروس
Good.
جيد
And kiss her.
وقبلها
Kaew.
كى كوان
Jate.
جيت
Don't be afraid. You're safe now.
لا تخافى,نحن بأمان الأن
where else can I escape to?
الى اين يمكننى ان أهرب؟
Please let me go to jail.
أرجوك دعنى اذهب الى السجن
Perhaps, it's what they want.
ربما هذا ما يريدونة
Listen to me,
أستمعى لى
Have some rest.
أرتاحى قليلاً
I'll take care of that.
أنا سأهتم بهذا
No matter how many coffins I buy,
بغض النظر عن عدد التوابيت التى سأشتريهم
they won't forgive me.
أنهم لن يسامحونى
They have to if we make an apology to them.
يجب ان يفعلوا اذا أعتذرنا لهم
Father, hello.
أبتى.مرحباً
Father
أبتى
Can I use the back room of the temple?
هل يمكنني استخدام الغرفة الخلفية للمعبد ؟
Let's go.
لنذهب
Jate, what do you want me to do?
جيت.ماذا تريدنى أن أفعل؟
What do you mean by apologizing to those people?
ماذا تعنى بالأعتذار لهؤلاء الناس؟
You'll understand when the time comes.
ستفهمى عندما يحبن الوقت
Jate.
جيت
Jate, help me.
جيت.ساعدنى
Let me out.
دعنى أخرج
Jate.
جيت
I'm sorry.
أنا أسفة
Please let me go.
أرجوكم دعونى أذهب
I didn't mean it.
أنا لم أقصد هذا
Please forgive me.
سامحونى
Father, no need to do a prayer.
أبتى.لاحاجة لأن تُصلى
It's useless.
انها بلا فائدة
You always act as a mirror for others.
كنت تتصرف دائما كمرآة للآخرين.
Do you ever think to reflect yourself?
هل فكرت فى انعكاس نفسك؟
Mirror reflecting mirror
مرآة تعكس مرآة
reflects nothing, Father.
تعكس لا شىء,أبتى
All we'd see is emptiness.
كل ما تراة هو فراغ
Make a lot of good merits.
أصنع العديد من المزايا
So your karmic debt won't be too heavy.
لذا ديونك لن تكون ثقيلة
I always do merits, Father.
أفعل دائما يستحق ، أبتى
Kaew.
كايو
Jate.
جيت
That woman.
هذة المرأة
She's my mother.
أنها أمى
My mom's dead since my dad..
أمي ميتة منذ والدي ...
I don't know who my real parents were.
انا لا اعرف من هم والداى الحقيقيين
My step dad took me from the hospital.
لقد أخذنى والدى من المشفى
I come back here
لقد عدت الى هنا
because I wanna know who I am.
لأنى أردت أن اعرف من أنا
Jate.
جيت
Why did she have to hurt me?
لما يجب ان تؤذينى؟
Perhaps, she wasn't there to hurt you.
ربما لم تكون هناك لأذيتك
Some spirits..
...بعض الارواح
Just want to be close to the ones they love.
فقط تريد ان تكون مقربة ممن تحبهم
When I was having the accident,
عندما كنت اتعرض للحادث
Why did she have to put her hand over my eyes?
لما كان يجب ان تضع يديها على عينى؟
I don't know.
لا اعلم
But I'm confident that..
...لكنى واثق من هذا
She's there to save you.
هى هناك لتنقذك
Do you know what that creaking sound was?
هل تعرف ما هو هذا الصوت؟
Something isn't meant to be known.
شىء ما لا يجب ان نعرفة
Or seen.
أو نراة
You must be so tired.
لابد انكِ متعبة جداً
Go to sleep now.
أذهبى للنوم الأن
From now on,
من الأن فصاعداً
You won't have any bad dream.
لن يكون لديكِ احلام سيئة
Jate.
جيت
Thank you.
شكراً
For helping me.
لمساعدتى
I think your mother's upset now.
أعتفد أمك منزعجة الأن
Go to sleep now.
أذهبى للنوم الأن
Be careful. Please be careful.
كونوا حذرين.أرجوكم كونوا حذرين
Sergeant, help me here.
رقيب ، ساعدني هنا.
Head quarter. From unit 2. Over
رئيس المنطقة من الوحدة2.حول
The dead's a Jane Doe.
المتوفاة جين دوى
Help me here.
ساعدنى هنا
Aged 20 years old approximately.
يتراوح عمرها  بين 20 سنة تقريبا.
Pale skin and tall.
شاحبة الوجه طويلة القامة
Roger that. She's been dead for roughly 24 hours.
روجر ذلك . انها كانت ميتة تقريبا ل مدة 24 ساعة .
So, Inspector, you've found the 2 bodies.
لذا مفتش.لقد عثرت على جثتين
This is the first one.
هذة هى الأولى
The other one is missing.
الأخرى مفقودة
What did you find?
ماذا وجدت؟
Inspector.
مفتش .
All along,
طوال الوقت
you eat snakes..
...انت تتناول الثعابين
As your main dish?
كطبقك الرئيسى؟
Yes.
نعم
Why? Do I look younger?
لماذا؟هل أبدو أصغر؟
Inspector, we've found it.
مفتش.لقد وجدناها
Another dead body?
جثة اخرى ميتة؟
We've found a camera. There's a memory card inside.
وجدنا كاميرا بداخلها بطاقة ذاكرة
Retrieve the data inside.
أسترد البيانات بداخلها
Perhaps we'd find some evidence for the case.
ربما نجد دليل للقضية
There're more.
هناك الكثير
Another dead body, right?
جثة اخرى.صحيح؟
We've found another computer.
وجدنا كمبيوتر أخر
It's under deep water.
انها تحت المياه العميقة.
Cat got your tongue, Mr.Lawyer?
القطة اكلت لسانك.ايها المحامى؟
I think this time..
...اعتقد هذة المرة
Your client won't be able to get away with her crime.
عميلك لن يقدر على الهروب بجريمتة
Inspector.
مفتش
Please tell your police divers to dive again.
أرجوك اخبر الغواصين ان يغوصوا مُجدداً
Dive deeper.
ان يغوصوا اعمق
Please. I'm begging you. I'll be back.
ارجوك.اتوسك لك.انا ساعود فى الحال
Jate.
جيت
Jate, what's the matter?
جيت.ما الآمر؟
Jate. Jate.
جيت,جيت
Where are you taking me to?
الى اين تأخذنى؟
Jum.
جوم
Trust me.
ثقى بى
And come with me.
وتعالى معى
Jate.
جيت
Jate, why are you taking me back to this place?
جيت,لما تأخذنى الى هذا المكان؟
Wait for me in the car.
أنتظرينى فى السيارة
Sergeant, check all in the perimeter.
رقيب ،تحقق من كل المحيط
M r.Lawyer.
سيدى المحامى
Why do you want my divers back into the river?
لما تريد ان يعود الغواصين للبحر؟
There's nothing down there.
لا يوجد شيء هناك.
Jate.
جيت
Jum.
جوم
Jum. Jum.
جوم. جوم
Calm down, Jum.
اهدأى.جوم
Come with me.
تعالى معى
What's he doing?
ماذا يفعل؟
Inspector. Please come this way.
مفتش.ارجوك تعالى هنا
What's the matter?
ما الآمر؟
We've retrieved the camera's memory card.
لقد استرجعنا بطاقة ذاكرة الكاميرا
What about the computer?
ماذا عن الكمبيوتر.؟
We can open it too.
يمكننا فتحة الأن
ExceHenL
رائع
Open it.
أفتحة
We can open the cover but not the computer.
يمكننا فتح الغطاء ولكن ليس الكمبيوتر.
But we can read its memory card.
ولكن يمكننا قراءة بطاقة الذاكرة الخاصة به.
We can open it. Can it be read by our computer?
هل يمكن ان يكون كمبيوتر.ملكنا
We can read it from our computer.
يمكننا قراءتى من الكمبيوتر
ExceHenL
رائع
Don't be afraid.
لا تخافى
Because this time..
...لأن هذة المرة
Won't be like last time.
لن تكون مثل أخر مرة
This time, you'll be safe.
هذةالمرة ستكونى بأمان
And you won't have to be afraid of anything.
ولا يجب ان تكونى خائفة من أى شىء
Bride and groom, slowly show them your love.
العروس والعريس ، ببطء يظهروا حبهم
Embrace each other. Kiss each other.
يعانقوا بعضهم البعض.يقبلوا بعضهم البعض
Show your love.
أظهروا حبكم
Jate.
جيت
I have something to tell you too.
لدى شىء أخبرك بة أيضاً
What's it about?
ما الأمر؟
Don't tell me that..
....لا تخبرينى هذا
I wanna get married, Jate.
أريد أن أتزوج جيت
Let's get married.
لنتزوج
Well, bride and groom. Next, we'll have a video shooting.
حسنا، العروس والعريس. التالى سيكون تصوير الفيديو
Give me a sweet moment. Get closer.
اعطونى ذكريات حلوة أقتربوا
Closer.
أقرب .
So much in love.
الكثير من الحب
Damn it.
تباً
Jate.
جيت
Jate, what happened to me?
جيت.ماذا حدث لى؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Why did she have to kill me?
لما كان يجب ان تقتلنى؟
I have no idea.
ليس لدى فكرة
I don't know how you and she..
....انا لا اعرف كبف انتى وهى
Linked with each other.
مرتبطين ببعضكم البعض
All I know is that..
كل ما أعرفه هو أن ...
She's Kaew's mother.
انها والدة كى كوان
Now you...
...الأن انتى
have gone to the other world.
يجب ان تذهبى لعالم الأخر
You should go to where you belong.
يجب ان تذهبى الى حيث تنتمى
And someday, you..
...ويوم ما.انتى
Someday,
يوم ما
We'll meet again.
سنتقابل مجدداً
Jate.
جيت
Jate?
جيت؟
Go help Kaew.
اذهب وساعد كى كوان
Kaew.
كوان
What are you doing?
ما الذى تفعلينة؟
Come back inside.
عودى الى الداخل
Jate.
جيت
Between me and your girlfriend,
بينى وبين صديقتك
Who do you love more?
من تحب اكثر؟
Why are you asking me like this?
لما تسألينى هكذا؟
My girlfriend's dead.
صديقتى ميتة
Tell me whom do you love more.
اخبرنى من تحب اكثر
I love you, Kaew.
أنا أحبك كوان
Finally you said it, Jate.
أخيراً قلتها جيت
Jun]!
جوم
Jum, what are you doing?
جومزما الذى تفعلينة؟
I'm having a revenge on the one who tore us apart.
انتقم من الشخص الذى قام بتفريقنا
Good bye, Jate.
وداعاً جيت
Jum! Jum!
جوم.جوم
Jate, it'd be wonderful if we had a child together.
جيت.سيكون رائع لو كان لدينا طفل
What are you saying, Gift?
جيف.ما الذى تقولينة؟
I don't like babies.
انا لا احب الأطفال
Gift, never mind.
جيف,لا تهتمى ابداً
If you still love Jate,
اذا كنتى تحبى جيت
I think you have to make a decision.
اعتقد يجب ان تتخذى قرار
Jum, I love you.
جوم أنا أحبك
I love you too, Jate.
احبك ايضاً جيت
I'm sorry. We did our best to save the baby.
أسف.لقد بذلنا جهدنا للنقذ الطفل
Jate.
جيت
Doctor, the patient has no pulse.
دكتور.المريضة ليس لديها نبض
Sir.
سيدى
Your daughter's dead.
لقد توفت أبنتك
Gift, my baby.
جيف,طفلتى
Let her go, Jate.
دعها تذهب جيت
Why are you holding her back?
لما تمسك يدها؟
Do you wanna die with her?
هل تريد أن تموت معها؟
Do you love her that much?
هل تحبها بهذا القدر؟
Kaew's Gift's daughter.
كى كوان هى
She's my daughter.
أبنتى
Do you still love her?
هل مازلت تحبها؟
Yes.
نعم
And Gift wanna kill us both.
وجيف ستقتلنا كلنا
What will you choose?
ماذا تختار؟
Between your life..
....بين حياتك
And your daughter's.
...وحياة أبنتك
Gift!
جيف
And if you really knew what's happening,
واذا كنت تعلم ما سيحدث
Would you choose to be alive?
هل ستختار ان تكون على قيد الحياة؟
Or dead?
أو ميت؟
Quite right.
صحيح
What can I choose?
ماذا يمكن أن أختار؟
This is consequence of what I've done.
هذا هو نتيجة ما قمت به .
It is about time...
...لقد حان الوقت
that I have to pay my debts.
لأدفع ديونى
Don't worry, Jate.
لا تقلق.جيت
I'll take care of you.
أنا سأعتني بك.
Isn't it irony?
أليست هكذا السُخرية؟
The one that's named as a walking karma mirror,
لشخص الذى يُسمة كمرآة القدر
a psychic like me
نفسية مثلي
never seea his own karma's results.
لن يرى نتائج قدرة
Or the karma of the one I love.
أو قدر من يحبة
It must be like a mirror reflecting mirror
يجب أن يكون مثل مرآة تعكس مرآة
What we see is emptiness.
ما نراة فارغ
From now on,
من الأن فصاعداً
I have to pay my debts.
يجب أن أدفع ديونى
To those people I owe to.
لهؤلاء الناس الذي أدين لهم